bestsexpositions.com 2015-03-19

# Privacy Policy - bestsexpositions.com

Thank you for visiting bestsexpositions.com, a site within the network of sites operated by Liquid Logic, Inc. (“Liquid Logic”, “we” or “us”) each of which have adopted this Privacy Notice.

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by Liquid Logic, Inc. and its subsidiaries.

BY USING THIS SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TO OUR PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSES STATED BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE.

 **Information Gathered**  
Liquid Logic collects personally-identifying contact information provided through optional, voluntary registration and services on our website

These may include:

  1. Registration for Site feedback, comments, and suggestions,
  2. Registration for downloads or members-only content,
  3. Registration for our newsletter.

We also track the IP address of the clients from which people who visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual users remain anonymous.

If you choose not to provide contact information or participate in a forum, you can still visit most of Liquid Logic’s web site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, downloads and services. Personal information gathered at Liquid Logic’s web site is the property of Liquid Logic, subject to and protected by the Electronic Communications Privacy Act. Liquid Logic will not sell, rent, swap, or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third party, except where required by law, a validly issued subpoena, or other judicial order. Any reports shared for the purpose of attracting sponsors for this site will be in aggregate, they will only include total numbers of individuals and basic demographic information.

 **Use of Cookies**  
What are cookies? Cookies are small pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Their purpose is to let us know when you visit our site and save preferences you set. Your browser can be set to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. Any information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you.

We want to be sure you understand that accepting a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any personal information about you. We know that a lot of people have concerns about cookies, but in talking with many of our users we feel that the benefit we both gain from their proper use is worthwhile. We value the relationships we have with our customers and future customers, so we respect these concerns.

 **Links to Other Sites**  
This Site contains links to other sites. Liquid Logic is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

 **Interactive Features**  
Liquid Logic encourages public discussion by offering users the option to comment on the articles hosted on this site. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Contributions in public discussions may also be republished on the Site without express permission from the original contributor.

 **Security**  
This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of information, but you should recognize that any such security measures are inherently limited. Liquid Logic will not be liable for any breach of the security measures on the Site or any loss, misuse or alteration of information resulting therefrom.

 **Contacting Liquid Logic**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at privacy_policy@bestsexpositions.com . All information you provide in any written communication will also be covered by this policy.

 **Your California Privacy Rights**  
Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding Liquid Logic’s disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us:

> Liquid Logic, Inc.  
>  PO Box 33162  
>  Las Vegas NV 89133  
>  Email: privacy_policy@bestsexpositions.com

Last Updated On: Wednesday, November 10, 2007
